<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientific programming languages</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/scientific-programming-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/scientific-programming-languages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scientific-programming-languages-and-environments&#34;&gt;Scientific Programming Languages and Environments.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As computers become more ubiquitous in physics research (and scientific research in general), the issue of which programming languages to use becomes more important. Factors which especially influence the importance of this question are&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;the increasing complexity of the tasks being programmed;
the increasing complexity and diversity of the machines being programmed;
the increasing use of graphical visualization and interfacing to scientific programs; and
the increasing number of the programming languages available in which to program. 

C and C++
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C is an interesting choice as a scientific language. It is extremely flexible and available on about every machine known to man. Also, one of the best C compilers (gcc) is available for free. Almost all visualization and user-interface packages support the C language. C is frequently taught as a first or second language in university computer-science departments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A long-standing gripe about C is that it produces slower code than does the equivalent Fortran. Nowadays, computer speeds are doubling every year or so, and C compilers don&amp;rsquo;t seem to be doing that bad compared to Fortran anymore (typical C code runs between 50 and 100% as fast as the equivalent Fortran, depending on the application). In light of this, I think it&amp;rsquo;s hard to discard C on the basis of the speed of the code it produces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s a good scientific programming language. The C language is fairly close to the hardware, and it is quite easy to make big mistakes in coding an application. These mistakes often don&amp;rsquo;t display themselves in small test cases, since they involve memory-management issues and the like. Also, programming large applications in C requires some degree of professionalism, meaning a fairly deep grasp of the language. As such, it is a bad language for mainstream scientific programming; typically only the creator of a program, or people with real expertise in computer programming, will be able to understand a large C application unless it is very carefully written.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe these comments also apply to C++ coding. The concerns about readability and professionalism apply perhaps even more strongly here than for &amp;ldquo;just C&amp;rdquo;. C++ has the advantage of being the most-popular object-oriented language, but it is also recognized as being a fairly cryptic one. Again, a certain degree of professionalism is necessary to program a C++ application which is understandable to others. Packages which automatically generate C++ code from user-specified pseudocode help alleviate the problem, but then we are faced with asking all users to use the same C++ generator, which is another problem of the same magnitude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above two are the &amp;ldquo;traditional&amp;rdquo; choices. I now turn to newer languages which are less well known in the scientific community.
Python
Python is an object-oriented, extensible, interpreted language. It runs on essentially all Unix systems, as well as on DOS/Windows platforms and on the Mac. It is free and comes with complete source code. It is very easy to begin using Python &amp;mdash; at a simple level, it resembles Basic and can be used interactively in the same way as Basic. However, it supports object methods and &amp;ldquo;scales&amp;rdquo; nicely. Scaling indicates the relative difficulty of writing small vs. large applications. The object facilities help and encourage one to write an application in small pieces. These small pieces can be put together to make the big program, and the small pieces can also be used in other applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of Python is its extensibility. One can write an object library in C, C++, or native Python, which can then either be dynamically or statically linked with the main Python system and used in Python programs. One can use this to make a programmable application, such as a data-plotting package. One would add a package to the interpreter which contained commands to set up your plots and to actually plot the data. This Python+graphics interpreter can be given a different name, such as &amp;ldquo;pygraph&amp;rdquo;, and invoked as a command. The interpreter will process the graphics commands and perform them. However, at the same time you can use any other valid Python command as a command to this graphics program! Thus one graphics input file for this program could first compute the result and then manipulate and plot it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The leap from this to having Python+package systems such as data-analysis programs, or experiment-control programs, is fairly obvious. This can also solve to some extent the above-mentioned dilemma about the use of C++. A professional programmer can produce a well-defined library package with a well-defined interface in C++, and this can be included into the Python programs for use. As Python is quite readable in much the same was as is Fortran, a &amp;ldquo;normal person&amp;rdquo; (i.e. someone who is not a professional programmer) can use this library in his programs. Both the professionals, who want the power and efficiency of C or C++, as well as the group who must use the result and be able to read and understand the program, can be happy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week (May 16 - May 22)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/weekmay16-may22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/weekmay16-may22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m very tired, I&amp;rsquo;m solving issues with moving. For some reason, the application is not signed for a long time. I will come every day until they sign&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week (May 9 - May 15)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/weekmay9-may15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/weekmay9-may15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided not to postpone everything for later, so I will be productive at the beginning of the week. Also this week, a test work on programming technology, strength and luck will take place for me&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with bibliography</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/working-with-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/working-with-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-working-bibliography-lists-all-the-sources-that-you-might-use-in-your-research-essay&#34;&gt;A working bibliography lists all the sources that you might use in your research essay.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A working bibliography lists all the sources that you might use in your research essay. It is a &amp;ldquo;working&amp;rdquo; document in two ways. For one thing, it will change throughout the research process—expanding each time you add a potentially useful source and contracting when you omit sources that turn out to be less relevant than you anticipated. Also, once you have written your essay, your working bibliography will evolve one last time, becoming your list of works cited. For another thing, you can use your bibliography to organize and keep track of your research &amp;ldquo;work.&amp;rdquo; To this end, some researchers divide the bibliography into three parts: (1) sources that they need to locate, (2) sources that they have located and think they will use, and (3) sources that they have located but think they probably won’t use.
Because you will need to update your bibliography regularly and because it will ultimately become the kernel of your list of works cited, you should consider using a computer. In that case, you’ll need to print a copy or take your laptop along each time you head to the library. However, some researchers find it helpful to also or instead use notecards, creating a separate card for each source. You can then physically separate cards dedicated to sources to be located, sources already located, and &amp;ldquo;rejected&amp;rdquo; sources. Just in case your cards get mixed up, however, you should also always note the status of the source on the card.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown language</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/markdown-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/markdown-language/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;markdown-is-intended-to-be-as-easy-to-read-and-easy-to-write-as-is-feasible&#34;&gt;Markdown is intended to be as easy-to-read and easy-to-write as is feasible.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Readability, however, is emphasized above all else. A Markdown-formatted document should be publishable as-is, as plain text, without looking like it’s been marked up with tags or formatting instructions. While Markdown’s syntax has been influenced by several existing text-to-HTML filters — including Setext, atx, Textile, reStructuredText, Grutatext, and EtText — the single biggest source of inspiration for Markdown’s syntax is the format of plain text email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To this end, Markdown’s syntax is comprised entirely of punctuation characters, which punctuation characters have been carefully chosen so as to look like what they mean. E.g., asterisks around a word actually look like &lt;em&gt;emphasis&lt;/em&gt;. Markdown lists look like, well, lists. Even blockquotes look like quoted passages of text, assuming you’ve ever used email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is not a replacement for HTML, or even close to it. Its syntax is very small, corresponding only to a very small subset of HTML tags. The idea is not to create a syntax that makes it easier to insert HTML tags. In my opinion, HTML tags are already easy to insert. The idea for Markdown is to make it easy to read, write, and edit prose. HTML is a publishing format; Markdown is a writing format. Thus, Markdown’s formatting syntax only addresses issues that can be conveyed in plain text.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week (May 2 - May 8)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/weekmay2-may8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/weekmay2-may8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I came home last week. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t bad, I even managed to do all the lab work and assignments. And the food appears at home by itself, I rested and slept well. I put 8 out of 10 this week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version Control git</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/version_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/version_control/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-version-control-and-why-should-you-care&#34;&gt;What is “version control”, and why should you care?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Version control is a system that records changes to a file or set of files over time so that you can recall specific versions later. For the examples in this book, you will use software source code as the files being version controlled, though in reality you can do this with nearly any type of file on a computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a graphic or web designer and want to keep every version of an image or layout (which you would most certainly want to), a Version Control System (VCS) is a very wise thing to use. It allows you to revert selected files back to a previous state, revert the entire project back to a previous state, compare changes over time, see who last modified something that might be causing a problem, who introduced an issue and when, and more. Using a VCS also generally means that if you screw things up or lose files, you can easily recover. In addition, you get all this for very little overhead.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>week (April 28 - May 5 )</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/weekapril28-may5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/weekapril28-may5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Who is it easy for now? So it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy for me either. I made labs, bought chebupeli. It was delicious, but then my stomach hurt&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Wowchemy, the website builder for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Wowchemy website builder for Hugo, along with its starter templates, is designed for professional creators, educators, and teams/organizations - although it can be used to create any kind of site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The template can be modified and customised to suit your needs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good platform for anyone looking to take control of their data and online identity whilst having the convenience to start off with a &lt;strong&gt;no-code solution (write in Markdown and customize with YAML parameters)&lt;/strong&gt; and having &lt;strong&gt;flexibility to later add even deeper personalization with HTML and CSS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can work with all your favourite tools and apps with hundreds of plugins and integrations to speed up your workflows, interact with your readers, and much more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-the-template-is-mobile-first-with-a-responsive-design-to-ensure-that-your-site-looks-stunning-on-every-device&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/master/academic.png&#34; alt=&#34;The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started&#34;&gt;Get Started&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;👉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/templates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a new site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📚 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalize your site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💬 &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/z8wNYzb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Chat with the &lt;strong&gt;Wowchemy community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hugo community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐦 Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/wowchemy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/GeorgeCushen&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@GeorgeCushen&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MadeWithWowchemy&amp;amp;src=typed_query&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;#MadeWithWowchemy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💡 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Request a &lt;strong&gt;feature&lt;/strong&gt; or report a &lt;strong&gt;bug&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;em&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⬆️ &lt;strong&gt;Updating Wowchemy?&lt;/strong&gt; View the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/hugo-tutorials/update/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update Tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/updates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;crowd-funded-open-source-software&#34;&gt;Crowd-funded open-source software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help us develop this template and software sustainably under the MIT license, we ask all individuals and businesses that use it to help support its ongoing maintenance and development via sponsorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-click-here-to-become-a-sponsor-and-help-support-wowchemys-future-httpswowchemycomplans&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;❤️ Click here to become a sponsor and help support Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s future ❤️&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of appreciation for sponsoring, you can &lt;strong&gt;unlock &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; awesome rewards and extra features 🦄✨&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ecosystem&#34;&gt;Ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/hugo-academic-cli&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo Academic CLI&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Automatically import publications from BibTeX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration&#34;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Check out the latest &lt;strong&gt;demo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/user-stories/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;view the &lt;strong&gt;showcase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of personal, project, and business sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Page builder&lt;/strong&gt; - Create &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/page-builder/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;widgets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;elements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit any type of content&lt;/strong&gt; - Blog posts, publications, talks, slides, projects, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create content&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/import/jupyter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jupyter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/install-locally/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RStudio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System&lt;/strong&gt; - Fully customizable &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;color&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font themes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display Code and Math&lt;/strong&gt; - Code highlighting and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LaTeX math&lt;/a&gt; supported&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrations&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://analytics.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Disqus commenting&lt;/a&gt;, Maps, Contact Forms, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful Site&lt;/strong&gt; - Simple and refreshing one page design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry-Leading SEO&lt;/strong&gt; - Help get your website found on search engines and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media Galleries&lt;/strong&gt; - Display your images and videos with captions in a customizable gallery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Friendly&lt;/strong&gt; - Look amazing on every screen with a mobile friendly version of your site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-language&lt;/strong&gt; - 34+ language packs including English, 中文, and Português&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-user&lt;/strong&gt; - Each author gets their own profile page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Pack&lt;/strong&gt; - Assists with GDPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stand Out&lt;/strong&gt; - Bring your site to life with animation, parallax backgrounds, and scroll effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Click Deployment&lt;/strong&gt; - No servers. No databases. Only files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wowchemy and its templates come with &lt;strong&gt;automatic day (light) and night (dark) mode&lt;/strong&gt; built-in. Alternatively, visitors can choose their preferred mode - click the moon icon in the top right of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action! Day/night mode can also be disabled by the site admin in &lt;code&gt;params.toml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Choose a stunning &lt;strong&gt;theme&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for your site. Themes are fully customizable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2016-present &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;George Cushen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Released under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/blob/master/LICENSE.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
